(Leonard:)Why would I want
to do that?
(Sheldon:)Excellent question.
(Sheldon:)Do you remember
what happened to the alien,
(Sheldon:)played by talented character
actor Frank Gorshin,
in the Star Trek episode "Let
That Be Your Last Battlefield"?
(Leonard:)Uh, Captain Kirk activated
the self-destruct sequence
and threatened to blow up
the Enterprise
(Leonard:)and kill them both
unless he gave in?
(Sheldon:)Affirmative.
(Sheldon:)Computer, this is
Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
(Sheldon:)Activate self-destruct sequence.
(Sheldon:)Code 1-1-A-2-B.
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Self-destruct sequence
activated.
(Sheldon:)What are you
gonna do, Sheldon,
(Leonard:)blow up the apartment?
(Sheldon:)That was my first thought,
but all my cool stuff is here.
(Priya:)So what happens
when it counts down?
(Sheldon:)Unless Leonard signs
the new agreement
(Sheldon:)in the next 41 seconds,
(Sheldon:)this computer will send an
e-mail to your parents in India
(Sheldon:)saying that you're in
a secret relationship